Just realized that there was a morning school
You can drop Chan Chao off at school.
Oh, Master Nan?
Where did the sister go?
Hey!
- Have you met Ploy yet?
- I can't find her.
Did a student named Busaban make
it to the exam this morning?
We do not have a student named Busaban.
Are you sure that's our major?
She sat here regularly.
I used this computer.
But that machine has been broken since the last semester.
Teacher, did you remember the wrong room?
They will get married tomorrow.
Stupidly, you got fooled again as usual.
You're suffering because of the husband.
So you can't stand to see other people happy.
You Buanga!
When Thep marries Ploy, you'll know.
Stop misunderstanding like this.
Is there anything?
Her royal highness will be
the host of the wedding for us.
The lady allowed Buanga to move here.
Because she want to build a honeymoon house
for her favorite daughter-in-law.
I don't know what's so good about that woman.
Her appearance can't even compare to Buanga's.
Or maybe it will cast a love potion on
both the lady and Mr. Thep.
Those who do wrong and think evil will one day
receive the consequences themselves.
If she was calm like this,
In a while, both mother and child
will definitely be thrown out onto the streets.
The Nora has this incantation.
How can you let other people hurt you alone?
You've to marry another woman.
Even though you have a wife, have children?
I'm scared. I'm not being disrespectful.
Don't do anything.
You guys die and forget everything.
Only I can remember.
Look at my face.
Hello, this is Chan Chao's father.
Aside from me and Chan Chao's mother.
The school must not allow anyone
to take Chan Chao anywhere.
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
Why didn't grandparents curse you?
Despite you vie for everything from me.
Why don't you go to hell?
I know what I used to do with you.
But if you let me go,
I will make a merit for you.
You stole what should be mine.
It's been too long.
So what do you want from me?
Your life.
Now I can't do anything.
But if I die without knowing what I did wrong.
I will become a vengeful spirit like you.
At that time, we would be able to fight together.
Then you will know how terrible my suffering is.
Sit.
People say that you're sick.
What's wrong?
I've a fever.
If you're sick, bring your child to me.
Later, people will say that I don't take care of you.
Thep has not returned for many months.
It was not fair to you.
If you want to say something, just say it.
You used to say that I was the first wife.
I'm suffering from my husband
and I want you to suffer too.
I will speak as a woman.
That is not a first wife.
We were born into a world of men
with women in their hands.
And women are just the property of men.
Actually, you are luckier than me and Ploy.
Because you still have options.
That you'll be with the man you love.
Or love you.
But I and Ploy have no rights.
Because we were born as a position and family.
That was forced to be just a wife.
If the husband love us, it's good.
But if the husband doesn't love us.
We can only be.
The treasures that adorn one's prestige.
You're still beautiful.
If you still have a choice,
Leave your child.
Then take this money and start a relationship
with a man who is worthy of you.
And he will only have you.
If you want me to go.
Let Thep come to talk to me.
If it is really his need.
I will go.
I won't take anything.
How is she?
No one is more arrogant than her.
You can't speak nicely to her.
Oh, Bunga.
Feeling better?
Yes.
You came at the right time.
Riam went back home to take care of her father.
- Could you please make some fish kidney curry?
- Sure.
Give him an inch, and he'll take a mile.
She came to help is good enough.
Yes, this is Mr.Thep's wife.
The husband has not been here for a long time.
Can you still call her wife?
Bunga,
How is dad?
Is he still angry?
Hurry and see.
Why?
What is wrong?
Where are you going in the morning?
My dad is sick. I will hurry to see.
Oh,
May he be okay.
His body is burning with fever.
Uncle Nui said,
He was sick since that day.
Kem,
Yes,
Brought it.
Chan,
Oh, don't cry.
Can you help?
It's okay.
How are you?
What?
Take your child home.
It will be dark, it will be difficult.
I'll be here until you get better.
Please tell Mok that I will be
back in two or three days.
Thep said that when you're sick,
do not sit in the house.
Come out to breathe the air and contact sunlight.
If you believe me,
As if believing the husband would be good.
I'm sorry.
I did it because I was bullied.
Sometime,
You're too hasty because you've not yet
discovered the cause.
Thought bad to him.
It will be a karma.
Another thing,
All rituals are not able to do it.
Especially cursing,
It's as lowly as killing.
If you misunderstand and kill an innocent person,
it is a great sin. Even if we kill an evil person who deserves to die, it is still a sin.
So what should I do?
You can only standing.
Get the results of the action.
But note that,
Everything has its price.
It's like you,
Choose a man who is different from us.
Buanga,
Want to go see a shadow puppet show at the temple?
Today they're also performing
the story of Kaew Nam Ma.
No, uncle. I'll go to bed.
Yeah, as you wish.
But if changing your mind, tell Dad to follow.
Today, the whole village came to see it.
- I'll go first.
- Yes,
Do you know?
Why did I give you the clock?
Because it means time.
Time is the most valuable thing.
Which cannot be called back.
Giving time.
Is to give a part of life.
As a Nora, you have to behave well.
Even if you don't become a monk,
you can't become a great Nora dancer.
But you have to behave well.
Have noble.
If you act like this, how can you face
the ghosts of your grandparents?
- No husband, isn't she?
- Where will the child come from?
Who would it be?
It's Kem,
I know who she's pregnant with.
Stop.
I don't know.
Oops, suddenly itchy.
This rash.
Buanga, have you given
the eggs to the lady to eat yet?
Well, you believe that I am a bad woman.
Believe that my child is not your grandchildren
so you find a way to eliminate me.
You dare to raise your voice at me?
If you're going to be this arrogant,
then I guess we don't have to care each others.
There are people.
Not a pig, not a dog,
how can she be imprisoned like this?
Or to send her home.
I won't go home.
I will wait for Thep here.
Since getting to know Thep.
I have been happy countless times.
Or all of this is the price that I have to pay.
Dad,
Chan,
There is nothing to rob this house.
If you want to get anything, then take it.
Please spare the three of us.
Send your child to me.
And I will keep your life and dad.
What are you going to do with my child?
My child is just a child of the villagers.
Someone wants your child.
Leave your child.
Then took this money to set up
with a man that is worthy for you.
And he will only have you.
I will kill you.
- Run,
- No,
- Go,
- Go now.
- Father, no.
If you touch my child,
Let's cross the body first.
Threatening me like that doesn't mean you're
looking at your physical condition, you old man.
You die.
I know that you are around here.
Regardless, you can't escape.
Buanga,
Slept yet?
I have a letter.
Buanga,
She may go to see the shadow play with uncle.
Teacher,
What happened?
Help!
Buanga,
Teacher,
Don't do anything.
Don't do anything to my child.
I begged not to do it.
Send your child.
Send child to me.
No.
Want to die?
I said send your child.
Don't force me do it.
Bring the child.
Baby,
Buanga,
What happened?
Why is she like this?
I don't know,
I woke up this morning and went to give
alms to the monks. I met that woman...
Miss Lukchan.
In front of the house.
And where is Buanga?
She went to her father house two days ago.
Or something will happen to that house.
And what should I do?
The lady is not at home too.
She'll go back tomorrow.
Go take a shower.
Yes.
Mok,
- Send people go to see Nora Jiam.
- Yes.
Jiam,
Sigh
Until now,
Jiam and Buanga is not showing up.
They may have been killed.
If they have been killed,
The body should have been found.
Or maybe it was captured for ransom.
If being captured for ransom,
Isn't it better grab the child?
Heard that the child appeared
at Luang Decha's house.
Go to my friend's house for a while.
If we stay in this area.
Sooner, Your lady's people must find us.
And will definitely not let us leave.
Ouch!
I'll go find something to eat.
Wait here.
Don't go anywhere.
To my Buanga,
In 15 days, I will return to Songkhla.
I want you and my child pick me up
at the train station.
Then we will talk to understand.
What happened in the past.
Love and miss, Thepparit.
It's time for you.
Returning to pay karma in hell.
And if I agree to die.
What are you going to do with the Thep and Chan Chao?
I'll go back together happily.
Three people.
Father,
Mother,
Daughter,
Ghost and human.
And do you think they want to be
happy with you or not?
You've to deceive him that you're a human forever.
Buanga, no.
Khem,
Is mommy here?
No, I came to do some business.
Wait here for a moment.
I knew
That...
What should I do with you.
Hey!
Finally you come,
Actually, I have to go to another place.
But a friend begged me to come and see you first.
The problem you encounter.
The police couldn't help.
What are you doing?
Don't hesitate.
Because if you change your mind
and come back next time.
We couldn't find each other anymore.
This necklace will help protect you.
I found my mother.
I warned you, right?
You said that my mom was in the house.
That...
Mommy,
Mr. Thep,
Ploy,
Lady,
Luang Decha,
Ploy,
She didn't answer.
(Thep)
(Missed Call)
Yes,
Have you met Ploy yet?
Not yet.
But she probably is in the house.
I'll call you and tell you that I got the CCTV files.
At every point, you are alone.
But it's like you're talking to someone.
Hey, if you're not crazy, it means that there is
another person that no one sees.
I think the person you meet is not a criminals.
And not a human too.
The more you are like this
I was even more worried.
I don't want to let you stay at home with child.
I'm fine.
It's like someone really forced me to do it.
I didn't.
I didn't really do it.
If you're tired, go to rest.
I'll take my child to bed.
Thep
Thep, listen to me first.
I didn't really do it.
- Thep Thep I think this house ...
- What's up?
I think the person you met.
She is not a human.
Ploy,
Let me go.
A little more.
Hang in there.
Ploy, are you okay?
A little more.
Where is Buanga?
Why didn't she come?
What did you do?
Why did Buanga and Khem have disappeared?
Since the night that Nora Jiam was dead.
Nora Jiam was dead?
I know you hates her.
But I don't think you are so sorrowful.
He must protect me.
Has he ever done it?
May he receive that karma.
May he fall into hell and never be reborn.
Khem and Buanga the major witness.
As long as we can't find them,
I'll not return to Bangkok.
No one believes.
No one sees.
But God will know what we've done.
Oops,
Oh my godness.
What do you want?
Let me go.
Get out.
Don't mess with my child.
Rest in peach, Buanga.
Liar.
People say that,
They were revenged by Buanga.